tomorrow, this is your third time around
here now. What is the mission, man? Um,
it's so much of an honor to come back
here
from what the Johnson's think of me, the
organization, [music] uh, AG, uh, Mooj,
for them to bring me back is such a
tremendous honor and very humbling.
leaving leaving one mission out of New
Orleans
uh and having peace about that mission
being finished and being able to step
into a new one. It's to help and be a
part of what's being built here. I think
AG has a very clear vision of how to
take an organization that has gone an
extended period of time without success
and move it into successful. Um he did
it in Detroit. it was a part of that and
now he's getting a chance to do it here
to a place that drafted him um that he
felt like he owed it to and I feel the
same
>> for us to win.
We can't have like them small little
issue we just have GET THE CALL CAN'T
HAVE THOSE we can have day one mistakes.
>> Can you speak to that relationship with
Aaron [music] because you've known him
for a long time. You were drafted in
2012. He was a scout here
>> and then you guys were together in
Cleveland.
>> And then finally New Orleans as well.
>> So you know him
>> not like a lot of the other guys who are
going to be in that locker room.
>> Yeah. I've gotten a chance to know what
he's about and he's gotten a chance
[music] to know what I'm about. And so
um we don't have to have a lot of
conversations about what's [music] the
mission and what's the objective. We
know what each other are about and uh
there's no one more equipped to lead
this organization at [music] this moment
than him. And I'm really excited about
being a part of it [music] and uh
serving alongside of him. There are
reinforcements that are being brought in
just to echo that mission and to echo
that voice [music]
and to to raise the volume up a little
bit uh that we [music] all can hold the
line and continue to walk because for
this thing to turn, [music] we just all
got to keep rowing in the same
direction.
>> TODAY WE TAKE THE HARD GROUND. TODAY WE
take the high ground. We got on this
boat. We had the clarity. We had the
confidence. We had the consistency.
[music]
But then we got out on the water and the
storms came. Great.
>> What has made you [music]
one of the better leaders of
professional sports? You were just in
New Orleans for eight [music] seasons
and an organization talked about you
unlike
many people will ever be talked about as
far as what you meant to everybody there
on the field, [music]
inside the locker room, in the
organization, and also out in the
community. I'm just very clear on who I
am and how I show up. My responsibility
in every environment is to show up as a
servant leader. It's about serving
[music] the people around me. And every
day I'm trying to get better at that. I
don't have that perfectly, but every day
I'm trying to get better at that.
[music] And the ways I try to show up is
number one, um being an elite player at
my position [music] is very important to
me. I believe that uh people follow what
they see, not what they hear. And so,
um, even [music] at 37, I'm going to, as
long as I'm playing this game, I'm going
to play it at a high level. That's
that's very important to me or that's
[music] what I'm striving to. And so, it
starts with my individual play, but then
it's about elevating the guys around me.
Like, how can I help take the defense to
the next level? And I [music] need to
understand all the position groups cuz
you're relating to people. And you got
to understand the assignments. You have
to understand what you're going against.
And you have to understand offenses
[music] cuz you can't defend what you
don't know. And so that's a lot of
study, a lot of prep. Um, [music] but
it's about bringing the unit along.
Pouring into people to help them take
the next step in their career is
something that I take a lot of pride in.
>> What flips for you on the field? Because
everybody knows he's
good friend, great teammate, [music]
great spirit. Well, he's a bad man on
the field. They call you a Terminator
for a reason.
>> I think I [music] respect the game and
you got to respect the game and it'll
respect you back. And so, um, I used
[music] to study all the old
linebackers, uh, Dick Buckus,
um, Mike Singleary, Ray Lewis,
uh, Brian Erlac. You got to just, you
just go back. Jack Lambert, and Patrick
Willis. I mean, I could go all day with
[music] these guys.
And when you look at how they played the
game, it was violent and ferocious. It
was about [music] enforcing your your
will upon the opponent. And that's how I
look at it. That's when I put my helmet
on and [music] I'm inside those white
lines. There's only one way that you can
play this game and it's 1,000 miles an
hour um with with relentless intensity
for four quarters or beyond [music]
until that final whistle blows.
It's great seeing you.
>> Great to see you, man. Super excited
about what's ahead.